When you're struggling in a match, don't
compare your worst game to your best
game. This internal chatter right here
can sound very familiar. Why does it
have to be so tough? I shouldn't have to
work for it so much. I'm better than
this. Why am I underperforming so badly
or even my best game is nowhere near
this? You see, first of all, all these
thoughts are taking you away from the
present moment. And secondly, you're
creating a huge gap between your current
game and your best game. Look, you're
the rock climber that's at the bottom of
the rock right now looking up. You can't
expect to just jump to the top. You got
to move your way, climb your way back to
the top. And you do that by focusing on
the process, not the result. What do you
need to do in order to execute a good
shot? Focus on the breath. Focus on the
steps that you need to take. So don't
compare your current game to your best
game. Start taking small action steps
and climb back up that mountain. Go for
it.